This is
an
awesome treasure
hidden at the end of the sea,
and anyone who finds it,
the King of the Pirates!
Is that exciting or what?
There are incredible adventures
out there just waiting for us!
Bon voyage!
Have the courage that sail and believe,
and we will see a glimpse of
the sun rising on our tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Back when we first started,
we had separate horizons,
sailed toward different dreams.
Things have changed now,
for together we found we looked
through the spyglass and see.
And we know that our hearts
have brought us here.
Where the compass points our destiny.
There's no looking back,
take the hell with me!
Bon voyage, we can't
stop all our troubles.
Forget the past.
Though the future's
unclear, we still can smile.
We know we'll get there.
No regrets, every tear that we've
cried only helps our dreams come true.
You and those dreams
are precious in my life.
A glimpse of the sun
rising on our tomorrow.
You listening, Pops?
Fatayama Brothers!
I did it! Huh?
Huh?
Duh, duh, duh, oh!
The City of Gold!
It was right here!
That bonehead!
He did it!
Unbelievably beautiful.
That sound is amazing! What is it?
It's come, as I always
knew it would. Destiny.
Ah, this was the ringing that Nolan heard.
Now I get it.
Yay!
Singing.
Listen.
The Fourth is singing a song.
So...
This is proof.
God is real.
This is surely a miracle.
I had almost abandoned hope
that we would ever hear
the Golden Bell again after
nearly 400 years of silence.
Great warrior Kal 'gara, can you hear it?
The unmistakable echo
of the fire of Shandora.
Good heavens!
What must have happened to this land?
What is that strange chiming?
Could it be the legendary bell?
Mont Blanc, Noland.
Can you hear the bell sounding
from beyond your grave?
May these chimes reverberate
all the way to your descendants.
Now rest in peace, Noland.
You like the bells ringing, too?
Yeah, I bet you do.
Old man, this is it.
Yeah, there's no doubt about it.
Only one bell in this
world could echo so far.
And with such emotion.
Awesome.
Absolutely.
You know those giants you see
in the cumuloregalus clouds?
The story goes a little
something like this.
Whenever a human inhabits the sky
and the sun's rays shine upon him,
his shadow is reflected on the deep
mist and then cast far across the earth.
horizon.
To onlookers, the shadow appears as if
it's a gigantic monster looming above.
You mean those aren't really giants?
They're actually somebody's shadow?
That would mean we've
already found irrefutable
proof that people do live in
the sky. Am I right? Yeah.
I once thought
the story was a meaningless fantasy
and dismissed it altogether.
But it seems there is truth
to this legend my ears
are filled with the resounding
cries of the golden bell
if a golden bell exists
then why not an entire city
noland was telling the truth
his reputation can finally be
redeemed and with it our family
name that's the reason you
rang the bell isn't it Kid
shrewd move you have my thanks.
I won't forget this
Hey, Cricket!
Are you sick? Are you hurt?
No, it's those kids.
I'm just glad they're safe.
I was...guess I was just so worried.
Look! Up there!
Hey, that's god shit!
Oh, thank you.
He's sunk!
God, Enru and his ship are...
falling.
The bell's ringing ignites
the fire of Shandora,
that long-gone city that took
pride above all in its prosperity.
The reverberations serve as the island's
song, proclaiming the end of the battle,
a melody longing to be
heard by the island?
and generations of its natives
and supporters for 400 years.
Although the journey of this restless
island seemed nearly endless,
time cannot fade even
its most distant memory.
For long ago, people entrusted their
words in the sound of the golden bell,
lacing each ring with
words of faith and hope,
which resounded across the distant sea.
my friends?
it rang.
hey i wonder if pops heard it?
yeah i'm sure he did!
We're right here.
Bind the ropes to the
strongest-looking trees!
Issie, were you scared, dear?
Surprise, your treasure.
So what? Who cares?
Lucky!
The others...
They're fine. Don't try to speak.
Who's that over there?
Am I still alive?
No, you have to be treated right away.
My wounds aren't that severe.
Really.
That guy, he needs more help than me.
Look after him.
It's true.
His body's worn out. He's dying.
Yeah, but he was trying to kill us.
We don't know him anything.
I know.
It doesn't make much sense, but he was
going all out just like the rest of us.
He's a hero? Seriously?
Who knows?
Um, help him, raccoon doggy
I'm a reindeer antler, see?
Don't worry, you'll survive.
Thanks, reindeer.
Yeah, you're going to overexert yourself.
Go rest with the blue sea people.
Very well, then.
I want you to go and gather the family.
I guess anything's possible.
Speaking of which, what do you think
happened to Eneru and the bell?
Don't know.
I guess they must have crashed.
So we have a city of
gold, but in name only.
Which just means that our
adventure in poverty continues.
I'd rather have dials over gold any day.
That's something we just
can't get from the Blue Sea.
I'm to the point where I'd
settle for some concrete news.
I hope Nami's all right.
And where's Conis?
This not-knowing is driving me crazy.
Do you think it's a good idea to leave
Wiper with the Blue Sea-Dwellers?
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
It appears Aissa has befriended them.
We'll just have to act quickly.
If our enemy wakes before
we leave, we're finished.
Gather those who can move and we'll banish
every last one of Eneru's
priests to the clouds.
Yeah!
So did you have a chance to patch him up?
Yes.
All he needs now is rest.
Huh?
Hey!
Nami!
Colors!
Luffy!
We're back!
I'm so glad you're okay!
I was afraid I wouldn't
see any of you again!
Ah, she was worried!
Please.
I'm glad you guys grabbed some food.
Where's it from?
We found the pre-storage locker on
our way back through the forest.
There was lots more!
But, uh, how did you manage
to find your way back down?
Well, Gum-Gum balloon!
Whoa!
Conis, where's your old man?
Yeah, well, he...
he protected me.
and then Enoru.
Don't tell me.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me too.
Me three.
You're supposed to be dead!
Sorry, I'm alive.
Father!
You were on the lower
level of the White Sea?
I found myself there after
being blasted from the ledge.
And I wasn't alone.
Countless others ended up in the same spot
while making their way towards Cloud End.
Yet as we speak, they too are now on the
journey back via the restored Milky Roads.
Of course, given that there's
no longer an Angel Island,
a new destination was chosen.
Upper Yard.
Thank you so much.
We owe you our lives, God.
Just gone, Fong.
I no longer go by that title.
You were all forced to work in a
place like this for six long years.
I'm sorry.
We lost Angel Island, the home
we were supposed to return to.
And like the Shendorians,
our birthright's now lost.
Is the battle really over?
God's army is gone, but I just don't...
My chief, do you really believe the
400-year rift can be mended so easily?
Boy, I stuffed myself.
Well, it's getting pretty late, you guys.
It's time to hit the ship.
Whoa, you're not talking
about leaving, are you?
Relax.
Usopp, can you believe what she just said?
Hardly. It's sick. I mean,
the thought doesn't even cross her
mind to go out and look for gold,
and she calls herself a pirate.
How do you two like fat lips
to go with your fat bellies?
It's time, and soon I will return.
To the wide open sky, the
perfect home for a god,
pristine and unobstructed.
Yes, and best of all, no
pests to get in my way.
I'll be sure no one gets near it.
My own private paradise.
A land boundless, exquisite.
It's just like a dream
which comes to life.
Maxim,
set sail and deliver me to my new floating
kingdom which shines
brightly in the night.
The land without end.
The endless birth.
Where am I?
Inside the ruins of Shandora.
Confall.
You shouldn't move yet.
You.
You're a Skypeian.
Rest. Chief.
Chief, we are all bound together,
made brothers by the war.
The Golden Belfry.
It's the Shandorian's sacred
duty to protect it to the end.
Listen, that's the sound of
war drums announcing battle.
There's the signal fire, too.
Patience, wiper.
Rest a while longer.
The heroism of our ancestors is clear.
But whatever violence happened in the
past, you must allow it to stay there.
Our future starts here.
This is our home now, and we
Shandians will make it a good one.
Yes, most often the call for
vengeance cannot be ignored.
But today, it has been drowned out by a
sea of voices screaming in celebration.
We did it!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
All right!
Yes! Yes!
Oh my god.
I can always hear your voice
while you wander far from home.
Gazing up at the sky, you
are just like the moon.
You'll never change as
you climb into the night.
But your reflection
waves when you disappear,
fading so silently.
Stay as you are, don't lose your way.
Let these words guide you,
don't ever look back.
Don't give up on your dreams,
they're windless nights.
They come to you again and again.
Until you see the journey through.
You may not turn, I
hope that you'll learn.
To put your past behind,
and just keep moving on.